♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
I was very brave when the doctor
gave me that shot,
wasn't I, Lois?
Yes, Peter, you
were very brave.
Even when I knew that he was
gonna give me the shot,
I just k-kept looking
at him in the eye
and talking to him
about my summer plans.
You did very good.
See, Peter? It
wasn't so bad.
Yeah, except for
having to sit next to
that screaming autistic lady
in the waiting room.
I don't know what you want!
I don't know how to help!
Hi, there. Excuse me.
I seem to be lost.
Can you guys help me?
Oh, my God.
Are you Ryan Reynolds?
From The Proposal
and The Change-Up
and a ton of upcoming stuff?
Yeah, that's me.
I was on my way to Newport
and I kind of got turned around.
Ofourse, Mr. Reynolds, we'd be
happy to give you directions.
You take 138
to the Jamestown Bridge,
and you're gonna follow the...
There's a fire truck.
Yes, I see it, Peter.
It's a fire truck.
And after the bridge,
just follow the signs.
Thanks.
Hey, what happened to your arm?
I just went to the doctor,
got my cholesterol checked.
Wow, why does a guy in his 20s
need to get his
cholesterol checked?
Oh, come on, now.
Oh, hey, I never got your name.
Uh, Peter.
Peter Griffin.
And I'm Lo...
Catch you later, Peter.
Wow, he was really nice.
Not like when I met
that bitch Shelley Duvall.
Hi, I'm Shelley Duvall.
Very nice to meet you.
Big deal.
Came right up to me, like
I was just dying to meet her.
Peter, you're gonna
have to let that one go.
Hi, Mrs. Janetti.
I'm here to pick up Stewie.
Oh, sure, Brian. He's in
the playroom with Gavin.
Gavin- that's
a stupid name.
And nobody likes you at school.
You're gonna be ugly
when you grow up.
And everything
in your house is cheap.
And it smells in here.
Oh, hey, Brian.
Bye!
That was fun.
I like Gavin.
Oh, yay!
This is such a great song.
Really?
Yeah, really.
I don't have to defend
Carrie Underwood to you.
She is doing
just fine without you.
Brian, I'm just going to sit
in the car till the song's over.
All right, but don't take to
long; it'll drain the battery.
Oh, shut up.
It's not draining the battery.
♪ I took a Louisville Slugger
to both headlights ♪
♪ I slashed a hole
in all four tires ♪
♪ Maybe next time he'll think
before he cheats ♪
I should be on Glee.
I should be on Glee!
♪ I might've saved a little
trouble for the next girl... ♪
Oh, my God.
I just drove.
That was amazing.
I can drive!
Now I can do a slow cruise past
my ex-girlfriend's apartment.
11:45 and the lights are on.
Doing it with
the lights on now, whore?
Don't mind looking at his body?
I love you so much, though.
Lois, that dog with the
different colored eyes is back.
Ew, and gross!
It looks like he's got a boner.
Peter, just leave him alone.
No, this is
what Bob Barker's been
talking about all these years.
Go on! Get!
Get out of here,
weird boner dog!
Hey, look who it is!
Hey, Ryan Reynolds.
What are you doing
in Cleveland's house?
Well, believe it or not,
they've decided
to shoot my movie
in Quahog instead of Newport.
I'm playing Hitler,
but he's a young Hitler
and he's got a rocking body.
It's called Hotler.
Ha! Color me seven
bucks lighter.
Hey, I'm so excited
that we're gonna be neighbors.
We should totally hang out.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Okay, I'm embarrassed.
I'm standing out here
without a shirt on
and my pajama bottoms are
riding insanely low on my hips.
Hey, how much money you make?
You'd think enough
for a shirt, right?
So I'm having this
housewarming thing tonight,
and I'd love it if you came by.
Anything beats what goes on
at my house Friday nights.
Hey, Lois, what's
going on here?
Oh, it's my book club, Peter.
Come join us.
Oh, okay!
All right, let's see,
new novel, new novel, new novel.
What's it about?
A guy...
a guy who loses everything,
but finds his soul in Canada.
All right, we're cooking now.
Cooking now.
And the whole book
is an e-mail
to his daughter, who's dead.
And his name will be Norm Hull.
Because he's just a normal guy.
But not everybody
will get that.
That's just for e scholars
a hundred years from now.
Okay, Rupert,
you ready to go for a drive?
Oh, my God, Rupert,
this is such a thrill.
Look at me, I'm driving!
I'm driving a real car!
I don't believe it!
Well, I'd say we need
to put on some tunes.
Hey, welcome back to
Weenie and The Butt on 97.1.
♪ 97.1 ♪
Ooh, Weenie and The Butt.
Just like the grown-ups
listen to.
And that was "Baby" by Justin
Bieber featuring Ludacris,
which means it's time to give
away some Justin Bieber tickets.
Oh, that's right, Butt.
Our fifth caller
will ween those tickets.
Hey, you know what, Rupert?
You know what I should do,
just, like, as a goof?
I should try to win those Justin
Bieber tickets just so I can,
like, tear them up or use them
to go to t concert.
Oh, it's ringing, Rupert,
it's ringing.
I'm too nervous;
they're celebrities.
You talk to them.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I'm in so much trouble.
Congratulations,
you're caller number five.
You're going to see
Justin Bieber!
Oh, sweet Jesus!
Yes! Jesse, I won!
Never say never!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Brian's gonna be
so mad at me.
What am I gonna do?
Okay, it's all right.
I'll just get a little bit of
paint and cover up the dents.
Unattractive women
do it all the time.
You look pretty today, Carol.
Thanks.
It's probably just
the dress and the makeup.
Ah, now that I look closer,
yeah, I think that's
what it is, too.
Hey, you made it!
And you brought a friend.
Great.
I'm his wife, Lois.
We actually met the other day.
Oh, sorry,
I- I meet so many people.
But there's really no way
you could know that.
Yeah, she's a housewife,
she don't know.
Whatever.
You got booze in here?
Is it me, or did she
just make that weird?
Please. It was
definitely not you.
Hey, is this shirt too tight?
I'm feeling really
self-conscious.
No, not at all.
So it-it looks good like
this? Yeah, it looks good.
Thanks.
I don't know what to say.
Hey, I got, I got, like,
an insider Hollywood
question for you.
Is, um, is "L.A."
short for something?
Ha! You're a riot.
Hey, hey, so what's
all this about,
everyone in Quahog
likes to tickle fight?
What is that?
What? I never heard that.
Yeah, apparently
it's, like, a thing.
It is?
Yeah.
I mean, they also said
that people who pretend
not to have heard
of it are chicken.
Well, I ain't no chicken.
One-nothing!
No, two-nothing!
Three-nothing!
Fight over!
Wow, you got a lot
of catching up to do,
and tomorrow night
in the dark, huh?
In the dark?
Yeah, if you say so.
Just don't tickle me
in my lower abdomen.
I'm super ticklish there.
Lower abdomen.
You're gonna wish
you never said that.
This might be
totally off the wall,
but are you doing
anything Thursday night?
You probably have
plans, anyway.
You know what...
Forget it, forget
it, forget it.
Blah. Nervous.
You know, Ryan,
most people take one look at me
and just assume that I have
plans, so I never get asked out.
But I-I frequently
don't have plans, so yes,
I would love to do something
with you on Thursday night.
Yes! Oh, my God, right now
would be the worst time
for you to tickle
my lower abdomen,
because it's so exposed
'cause I'm cheering.
Yeah, Thursday night!
Aw, your big mouth
just got you in trouble.
Aw, I lose.
Peter one, you zero.
Oh, I lose again.
Peter two, you zero.
You've been practicing.
We now return to the end of
a depressing 1970s sci-fi movie
starring a guy in a turtleneck.
We've gone far enough.
I think we're safe from
The Corporation here.
Adzin, ook!
It can't be.
No!
We'll never defeat
The Corporation!
They've won!
There is one way, Adzin.
You can shoot yourself.
If it's the only way, I must.
What the hell?!
Stewie, get out here!
Look at this.
Do you know anything
about this?
A- About what?
About what
a beautiful day it...
Oh, my God, that is surprising.
Oh, I had to stop that
last sentence in the middle
because I was so surprised.
What happened?
Gee, I don't know.
Do you know what happened?
I'm sorry, w-what was that?
I- I was laughing
at that funny thing
you said at dinner
the other night.
What funny thing?
Um, y-you remember
what you said
about Lois's, um,
"patoes au rotten"?
Huh. Didn't ink
anybody heard that.
Wish you'd laughed at the time.
W- What the hell
happened to my car?!
Well, I don't know, man,
but the good news is,
it-it doesn't look
all that bad, Brian.
It's just,
it's that spot right there
that's upsetting you, right?
Stewie, I know it was you.
Your potato joke was terrible.
I can't believe
you drove my car!
You could have
gotten yourself killed!
I'm gonna have to tell
Peter and Lois.
No! No, you can't tell them!
I'll be in so much trouble!
Stewie, I have to.
All right,
I have covered for you
plenty of times before,
but not this time.
This is very dangerous,
and have to make sure
you never do it again.
I won't, I swear!
Stewie, calm down.
Sometimes in life you just have
to accept what's coming to you.
Like the contestant
who gets the lesser showcase
on The Price is Right.
Lindsay, your showcase
is all about relaxation.
And what better place to relax
than in your brand-new hammock?!
This sturdy and portable hammock
from Swingway turns any patio
into a tropical paradise.
And you can entertain yourself
on your patio
by drawing with chalk!
Yes, Pratt and Millwood
eight-color pastel chalk
will turn your patio
into a tropical art studio.
But you'll have
to pack your chalk
because you're going
to be staying
six days and seven nights
at your parents' house
in Wilmington, Delaware!
I moved my abortion for this.
♪ ♪
Um, hey, thanks for taking
me out to dinner, Ryan,
but I got to say, this
food looks a little weird.
Aw, Peter, Moroccan food
is the jizz.
I don't know. Looks like it
might give me the kind of farts
I get from eating Mexican food.
Con cuidado es el stinko!
Hey, do these pants
look all right?
Sometimes I put them on, and
I'm thinking I look all balls.
No, I think you're good.
You think my balls are good?
You're so weird.
It's awesome, though.
Oh, I... I don't know.
Hey, have you noticed
what a jerk the mailman is
in this town?
Like, he said there is no way
Peter Griffin
could crush a baby bird
with his bare foot
while I watched.
That guy talks
more crap about me.
Mmm! Oh!
Mmm. You got to taste
this lamb tagine.
Mmm. Here.
No, that... no,
that's okay.
Come on, you'll love it.
Eh...
Just a taste.
That was... intense.
What you just did.
Lots of...
Lots of flavors.
Whoops.
Whoa, freeze frame!
What's gonna happen next?
I think I got to
go to the bathroom.
What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna be in so much trouble
when they find out
I wrecked Brian's car!
They'll probably ship me off
to Siberia.
This sucks.
I hate it here.
Shut up.
Drink wolf milk and
watch Russian cartoons.
MAN WITH RUSSIAN ACCENT: We now return to
popular Russian cartoon, Shoe and Shoelace.
Shoe and Shoelace!
One is meaningless
without the other!
Well, that's it.
I have nchoice.
I've got to run away.
Guess I'm on my own now, Rupert.
It could be worse, though.
At least I'm not getting stabbed
by some random guy
on the street.
See? It's the exact opposite.
Oh! It happened anyway!
Hey, Stewie, you up?
What the...
Brian, I've decided to run away.
Don't come looking for me.
And definitely don't chase me
to the airport
and catch me at the gate
just before I'm about
to get on the plane
with, like, an emotional speech
and possibly flowers.
For example, it would be awful
if all the TSA people were
gathered around,
watching this emotional moment,
even the older black female
carry-on scanner
who initially stopped you
at the baggage check,
but who after you told her
of your intentions, said,
"Go get him, child,"
in flagrant disregard
of all newly-implemented
post-9-11 security measures.
And if you were considerin
bringing a boom box
to play music, I would suggest
any one of these six songs.
So again, ran away.
Don't come after me.
♪ I want to thank you... ♪
Dirty whores, all of you.
Oh, hey, Peter.
Lois, we got a problem.
I think Ryan Reynolds
is in love with me.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
It's true. Last night we were
at this restaurant,
and he tried to gay kiss me.
I'm telling you,
he wants to get with me.
Peter, come on.
Why would any man dress well,
groom himself and lift weights
just to sleep with other men?
He's not gay.
Well, I don't care what you say.
He likes me.
And we do have chemistry,
I- I won't deny that.
I- I... I will take
responsibility
fomy part in this.
I'm just gonna go over there
and let him down easy.
Oh, Snooki died.
Last stop.
What? This isn't the airport.
Oh, my God, Rupert!
We've got to get out of here!
Aah! Damn it!
Oh, no, no.
Baby fall down!
Is that...? Is that Consuela?
Baby all alone in street.
I take baby home.
It's me. Stewie.
Don't you remember?
You used to clean for us.
We used to make you use the
bathroom at the gas station.
Hey, you!
Uh, hey, Ryan.
Uh, bad time?
Um, perfect time.
Come on in.
I was just oiling my legs.
So, hey, what's on for tonight?
You know, my dentist
leaves his office unlocked.
I was thinking we
could do some nitrous
and then have dinner in there.
Look, Ryan, you're a great guy
and everything,
but I don't like you
in that way.
I mean, there are some things
that I would do with you,
but my heart wouldn't be in it.
What are you talking about?
That you like me,
and you want to be my boyfriend.
You think I'm gay?
Where did you get that?
Uh, uh, you-you tried
to kiss me.
Peter, I'm not gay.
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Look, look, look, let me...
let me put it to you this way.
I'm attracted to you in the way
that a man is attracted
to a woman, but I'm not gay.
When you live out in
Hollywood, you learn
that life is about different
spirits and energies
you meet along the way.
I just thought maybe our spirits
could intertwine, you know?
Ouenergies could merge.
Like my spirit could go
up inside your energy.
I- I have so much to learn
about show business.
But you know what?
I could never really be
attracted to somebody
who uses labels like
"gay" and "straight."
Maybe you should just go.
Well-Well, now,
wait a second.
What do you mean?
This isn't working.
It was a nice thought,
but I think we should
go our separate ways.
No, Ryan. I get it now.
I can be what you want.
We could...
Peter.
Don't embarrasyourself.
You need to just let this go.
Tickle fight! Tickle
fight! No, Peter, no!
Tickle fight! Tickle fight!
Tickle fight... Peter, no! No!
Oh, my God...
It's time for you to leave.
I can change.
I'm sorry, Peter.
We're done.
We can never talk again.
Here's a cell phone
so we can always talk.
Don't you guys
have any tub toys?
Here. Is rattle.
This is prescription
medication.
And it's not even
your name on the label.
What... What is this?
What's in this tub?
Is jicama.
Jicama?
And what is...?
What...? What...?
This is a chicken leg.
Are you also making soup?
For quincea├▒era.
Big party. Many peoples.
Oh, my God.
Hay un perro aqui.
┬┐Doggy es aqui?
I bet even you guys
don't watch George Lopez.
Consuela?
Hey, it's Brian.
I'm-I'm looking for Stewie.
No, no baby aqui.
I peed in your soup.
Happy 15th birthday.
Which, by the way,
is not a special occasion
in the normal world.
Stewie, I've been worried sick.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Brian? How did you find me?
I used my nose,
which I always forget about.
Come on, let's go.
No, I'm not going
back! I can't!
They're gonna be mad at me!
I didn't tell anyone.
You... you didn't?
No, I didn't.
Look, I thought about it,
and to be honest,
it's probably my fault for
leaving you alone in the car.
And if you promise never to do
it again, I won't say anything.
Okay, I promise.
My baby!
What?
I say, let go of me.
Consuela, we're leaving.
My baby!
Hey, she says
it's her baby, man.
Now, get out of here.
Is my baby. Ernesto.
No, I'm not...
I'm not Ernest...
Okay, this is so messed up
right now.
I did not want
to have to do that.
They were very nice
to me up until then.
Peter, stop staring
outhe window.
Ryan's gone.
He finished his movie,
he's moved out.
How could I have been so blind?
How could I not have seen
what he offered?
I think the whole
thing was very strange.
He thought you were strange!
How about that?
Whatever.
I just can't help but wonder...
will I ever see him again?
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru